David Dietz Papers
David Dietz Papers
- Scrapbooks
  - 1961 May 15-1962 Mar 30 (Package 22)
  - 1962 Mar 29-1963 May 21 (Package 22)
  - 1963 May 22-1964 Feb 26 (Package 23)
  - 1964 Feb 27-1965 Mar 16 (Package 23)
  - 1965 Mar 17-1966 Feb 15 (Package 24)
  - 1966 Feb 14-1967 Jan 17 (Package 24)
  - 1967 Jan 30-1968 Mar 12 (Package 25)
  - 1968 Mar 14-1969 Apr 1 (Package 25)
  - Apollo, First Moon Landing, 1969 Apr 7-1970 Mar 5 (Package 26)
  - 1970 Mar 6-1971 Feb 16 (Package 26)
  - 1971 Feb 18-1972 Mar 7 (Package 27)
  - 1972 Mar 8-1973 Apr 20 (Package 27)
  - 1973 Apr 23-1974 Apr 26 (Package 28)
  - 1974 Apr 30-Aug 5 (Package 28)
  - 1974 Aug 6-1975 Jul 18 (Package 29)
  - 1975 Jul 17-1976 Feb 20 (Package 29)
  - 1976, Feb 23-Nov 1 (Package 30)
  - 1976 Nov 1-1977 Apr (Package 30)
  - "Atomic Theory-Solar System" series of articles by David Dietz (Package 31)
  - Biographical, 1921 (Package 32)
  - Current Issues of Day, 1922-1926 (Package 32)
  - Feature articles and star maps, 1932-1935 (Package 33)
  - Feature stories, 1936-1939 (Package 33)
  - Untitled miscellaneous scrapbooks on submitted articles dealing with specific science topics, 1951 Sep-1952 Nov; 2 volumes (Package 34)
  - Untitled miscellaneous scrapbooks separated into categories for best feature story series, columning, series in a specialized field, and specialized series., 1954-1958; 7 volumes (Package 34)